<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>MSWord - Tag - Power Platform Tips &amp; Tricks</title>
        <link>http://example.org/tags/msword/</link>
        <description>MSWord - Tag - Power Platform Tips &amp; Tricks</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 14:27:14 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/msword/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Setting restrictive security on a Word Template while leaving sections open (Restrictive editing)</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/restrictive-editing-word/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 14:27:14 &#43;0000</pubDate><author>
                        <name>Nathalie</name><uri>https://nathalieleenders.com</uri><email>info@nathalieleenders.com</email></author><guid>http://example.org/posts/restrictive-editing-word/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/posts/restrictive-editing-word/Microsoft-Word-Logo.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Another Word tip, oh my…This explains how to set security on a Word document, restrict the editing, but allow forms to be filled out, and certain sections to be edited. For example, to add in attachments or images.
It’s the most frustrating process, but I hope I can explain it clearly.
If you find you cannot add a continuous break, but it does a page break, check out this article, or redo your document (that’s what I did)]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Business Process Flow - How to automate moving through different stages</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/bpf-automation/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 14:27:14 &#43;0000</pubDate><author>
                        <name>Nathalie</name><uri>https://nathalieleenders.com</uri><email>info@nathalieleenders.com</email></author><guid>http://example.org/posts/bpf-automation/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/posts/bpf-automation/power-autoamte-vs-flow.webp" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>How to move stages automatically (BPF) using Power Automate (no http calls needed)Quick summary: You need to grab data from 3 different tables, link them using lookup columns, capture ID’s, and add in conditions and use Data operations to shape the data into usable steps. Then add in a switch depending on your stage names, and add final actions updating your BPF table.
Sounds easy enough right?…..
Beaker&rsquo;s head on fireI hope this helps, and I tried explaining it clearly, please let me know in case of any questions, feedback, other methods etc.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to repeat words in Microsoft Word (XML Mappings)</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/repeatwordsinmsword/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 14:27:14 &#43;0000</pubDate><author>
                        <name>Nathalie</name><uri>https://nathalieleenders.com</uri><email>info@nathalieleenders.com</email></author><guid>http://example.org/posts/repeatwordsinmsword/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I know I usually only do Power Platform, but Microsoft Word is bound to be in your project needs someday, or combining with Power Automate, so I figured why not?
Ever had the request to have certain words repeated, lets say in a header or footer? It can be anything, a date, name, product title, Business Unit etc etc.
This can be achieved using XML Mapping in Microsoft Word. To get to the XML mapping, you must first have the Developer Tab activated.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
